rajah.com 2016-05-14

# WWE News, Rumors, Results, Spoilers @ Rajah.com

At RAJAH.COM we are committed to providing you information tailored to your individual wants and needs. We also recognize the importance of protecting personally identifiable information relating to you, our users and subscribers. RAJAH.COM does not collect personally identifying information about individuals, except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may request your name, street, and e-mail address to aid in our administration of the contest and to assist in contacting the winners. 

RAJAH.COM utilizes specialized "Server Software" to automatically collect information about which pages each user visits as well as the user's Internet Service Provider (e.g., aol.com). This information is used for internal review, to tailor information to individual visitors and for traffic audits. 

Under no circumstances will we give specific, identifiable information about our users to outside third parties. However, we will, from time to time, provide advertisers or potential advertisers with aggregated, anonymous information about our users. In addition, any personally identifiable information provided by subscribers as part of an advertiser promotion within www.RAJAH.COM may be provided to such advertisers as needed for the reasonable administration of the promotion. 

At this time, RAJAH.COM discourages the use of "cookies" throughout the Site. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can access and enjoy virtually all of the features of our Site. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve our ads on the Internet. These third-party advertising companies employ cookie and 1x1 pixel .gif technology to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their clients. To do so, these companies may use anonymous information about your visits to our Web site and other Web sites. This information can include: date/time of banner ad shown, the banner ad that was shown, their cookie, the IP address. This information can also be used for online preference marketing purposes. 

If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from setting and/or reading cookies on your computer, currently you may either visit each ad network's web site individually and opt out or visit the NAI gateway opt-out site to opt-out of all network advertising cookies. Click [here ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp) for the NAI gateway opt-out site. This site will also allow you to review the third-party advertising companies' privacy policies. 

A user's personally identifiable information (e.g., name, e-mail address) may be required in certain instances. For example, if we run competitions or contests on the site, you may be required to provide information such as your telephone number and address in order to participate. The exact rules may vary in each case but the specific rules for any contest will state how that information may be used. We may also use personally identifiable information for marketing and promotional purposes. RAJAH.COM may send you e-mail alerting you to new features, products, promotions, or services pertaining to our site as well as on behalf of our various sponsors. 

We do not control the privacy policies of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which we provide hyperlinks. Users should also be aware that, when you voluntarily disclose personal information in chat areas, bulletin boards, or other public forums, such information may be collected by others and may result in the receipt of unsolicited messages. 

Children: Be sure to ask your parents for permission before you send any information about yourself - like your name, address, or e-mail address - over the Internet, to us or to anyone else and before making any purchases online. 

Parents: We encourage you to get involved with your children's online usage and to be aware of the activities in which they are participating. Any personally identifiable information collected by RAJAH.COM from children (that we are aware are children) will be used only for the internal use of RAJAH.COM. Such use may include market research, prize verification, contest fulfillment or requests for information or materials, and may sometimes be included in our database. Such information will not be posted or published by us, or provided to any third parties, without your prior consent. Anonymous aggregated data is sometimes provided to other parties which we do business with, for statistical and market research purposes as described above. 

Finally you should be aware that if your child voluntarily discloses his or her name, e-mail address, etc. within various public forums (including bulletin boards and chat rooms), such disclosures may result in unsolicited messages from other parties. 

Technology on the Internet is developing at a fever pace. It is critical that RAJAH.COM maintain its ability to rapidly adjust these policies in the future. By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by RAJAH.COM. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

1/14/02 UPDATE: 

Third Party Advertising 

We use DoubleClick and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). 

Third Party Cookies 

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique �cookie� on your browser. 

8/20/02 UPDATE: 

Third Party Advertising 

We use MaxWorldwide and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). 

Third Party Cookies 

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique �cookie� on your browser. 

5/19/04 UPDATE:

Third Party Advertising

We use MaxOnline and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here](http://www.maxonline.com/privacy_policy/index.php).

Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique �cookie� on your browser. 

June 2012 Update 

The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on the publisher's site(s) and across the web. 

* Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.   
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.   
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising opt-out page [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

We welcome your questions and comments about our privacy policy. If you would like to drop us a line, please email [privacy@rajah.com](mailto:privacy@rajah.com)

This site uses cookies to deliver its services, to personalize ads and to analyze traffic. Information about your use of this site is shared with its partners. By using this site, you agree to its use of cookies. For details, click [here](http://rajah.com/privacy.php).
